Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Editorial Records 1944-2003 (bulk 1959-1994) MS 3009-RG 6
New-York Historical Society
- Series II.F. Editorial Director General Files, 1978-1989; 8.5 Linear feet in 10 record cartons
  - Contract: Newstour Book: David Aikman: November 20, 1985, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 24)
  - Contract: Newstour Book: David Aikman: November 20, 1985 [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Contract: Roache, Pat, 1986 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 25)
  - Contract: Roache, Pat [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Contract: Rosenblatt, Roger: General, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 26)
  - Contract: Rosenblatt, Roger: Children of War [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Contract: Ryan, Patricia [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R12)
  - Contract: Worrell, Denise: Atlantic Monthly Press [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Offsite-box R12)
  - Contracts: Consultants, 1987 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 27)
  - Contracts: "Talent", 1988 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 28)
  - Coordinator's Job Description, 1987 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 29)
  - Corporate Administration, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 30)
  - Corporate Aircraft, 1988 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 31)
  - Corporate Contributions, 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 32-35)
  - Corporate Cultural Affairs, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 36-37)
  - Corporate Edit Financial Officer, 1986 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 38)
  - Corporate Editor Job Description, 1987 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 39)
  - Corporate Estimates, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1338, Folder 40)
  - Corporate Management Committee, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 1)
  - Corporate Public Affairs, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 2)
  - Corporate Trainees, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 3)
  - Cost Cutting Ideas, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 4)
  - Cost Management, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1399, Folder 5-7)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 8)
  - Cross-Over Candidates, 1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 9)
  - Edit Technology, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 10-15)
  - Edit Technology [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Editor in Chief: The Role of, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 16)
  - Emerge, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 17)
  - Ergonomics Guide, 1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 18)
  - Errors Control, 1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 19)
  - ESOP (Benefits), 1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 20)
  - Estimate: Monthly, 1985 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 21)
  - Executive Briefing Lunches, 1985 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 22)
  - Executive Degree Programs, 1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 23)
  - Expense Account Policy, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 24)
  - Expenses: Magazine Group by Month, 1985 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 25)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 26)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - First Class Travel, 1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 27)
  - Fortune, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 28-29)
  - Fortune [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Freelance Employees, 1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 30)
  - FYI, 1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 31)
  - Gardner Reports on Finances, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 32)
  - Graphics on Deadline, 1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 33)
  - Graves, Ralph, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 34)
  - Grunwald, Henry: Budget, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 35)
  - Grunwald, Henry: Dinners, 1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 36-38)
  - Grunwald, Henry: Editorial Briefing Lunch, 1986 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 39)
  - Guild: General, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 40-41)
  - Guild: Negotiations, 1976-1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 42-43)
  - Halvey, David [RESTRICTED], 1986-1987 (Offsite-box R12)
  - Home Box Office [HBO], 1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 44)
  - Headcount, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 45)
  - Heiskell Awards, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1339, Folder 46)
  - Henchel, Barbara, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 1)
  - Henchel, Barbara [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Hill, Andrea [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Offsite-box R12)
  - Hiring Freeze: Discover, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 2)
  - Hiring Freeze: Edit Services, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 3)
  - Hiring Freeze: Exceptions, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 4)
  - Hiring Freeze: Fortune, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 5)
  - Hiring Freeze: Fortune [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Hiring Freeze: Life, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 6)
  - Hiring Freeze: Money, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 7)
  - Hiring Freeze: People, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 8)
  - Hiring Freeze: Sports Illustrated, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 9)
  - Hiring Freeze: Time, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 10)
  - Legal [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986 (Offsite-box R12)
  - Magazine Development: General, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 4-6)
  - Magazine Development: Personnel, 1986 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 7)
  - Magazine Group: Total Edit Expenses: 1985, 1986 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 8)
  - Magazine Group: Weekly Report Final, 1985 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 9)
  - Magazine Manufacturing and Distribution (MM&D): General, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 10)
  - Magazine Manufacturing and Distribution (MM&D): Edit Technology, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 11)
  - Magazine Manufacturing and Distribution (MM&D): Impact Center, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 12)
  - Management Development Committee, 1987 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 13)
  - Management Directory, 1987 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 14)
  - Management Training, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 15)
  - Managing Editors: Miscellaneous, 1986 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 16)
  - Managing Editors: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Managing Editors: Lunch, 1986 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 17)
  - Managing Editors: Memoranda, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 18)
  - Managing Editors: Responsibility of, 1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 19)
  - Martin Project (Peter Bird), 1985 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 20)
  - Mastheads and Publetters, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 21)
  - McCalls / Working Woman: Dale Lang Inc., 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 22)
  - McManus, Jason, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 23)
  - Media on Time Inc., 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 24)
  - Meeting: Greenwich: June 8-9, 1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 25)
  - Meigher, Christopher, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 26)
  - Meyers, Jack, 1986 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 27)
  - Missouri, University of, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 28)
  - MIT Media Laboratory, undated (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 29)
  - Money, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1927, Folder 30-31)
  - Morris-Everett Cases, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 1)
  - Morris-Everett Cases [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Muller Report on News Service, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 2)
  - Mulvoy, Mark, 1988 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 3)
  - Munro, J. Richard, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 4)
  - NASA Journalist in Space Program, 1985 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 5)
  - New Magazine Ideas, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 6-7)
  - New Magazines: General, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 8-9)
  - New Magazines: Acquisitions, 1987 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 10)
  - New Magazines: Entertainment, 1988 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 11)
  - New Magazines: Family Wealth, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 12)
  - New Magazines: Health [empty], undated (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 13)
  - New Magazines: Home Office, 1986 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 14)
  - New Magazines: Leisure, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 15)
  - New Magazines: People, Jr., 1986 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 16)
  - New Magazines: Quality, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 17-18)
  - New Magazines: Real Estate, 1987 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 19)
  - New Magazines: You (Sports Illustrated), 1986 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 20)
  - Newsmagazine Ideas, 1986 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 21)
  - News Service, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 22)
  - Newsstand Sales, 1988 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 23)
  - NewsTime, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 24)
  - Newstour: USSR, 1987 (Offsite-box 1928, Folder 25)
  - Nexis, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 11)
  - Nexis [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Nicholas, N. J., Jr., 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 12)
  - O'Neil, Doris: Projects, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 13)
  - O'Neil, Doris: Projects [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - O'Neill, Michael, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 14)
  - Operating Reviews: General, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 15)
  - Operating Reviews: Editorial, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 16)
  - Operations: Edit Services, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 17)
  - Operations: Fortune, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 18)
  - Operations: Life, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 19)
  - Operations: Money, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 20)
  - Operations: People, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 21)
  - Operations: Sports Illustrated, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 22)
  - Operations: Time, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 23)
  - Overtime Issue, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 24)
  - Overtime Issue [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Parenting, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 25)
  - People, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 26-27)
  - People [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Picture Policy, 1977-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 28-29)
  - Picture Policy [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Planning Committee [Strategic Plan], 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 30)
  - Presidents' TV Show Project, 1985 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 31)
  - Production Ad-Edit Task Force, 1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 32)
  - Raise Approvals, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 33)
  - Raise Approvals [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Raise Freeze Exceptions, 1986 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 34)
  - Raise Freeze Exceptions [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Raise Review Changes: Fortune, 1986 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 35)
  - Raises: Special Adjustments [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Rauch, Ru, 1986 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 36)
  - Reader's Digest Contract, 1979-1982 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 37)
  - Reader's Digest Contract [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Readers' Letters, 1985 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 38)
  - Restructuring: General-Important, 1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 39)
  - Restructuring: Cost Cutting, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 40-41)
  - Restructuring: Discover, 1986 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 42)
  - Restructuring: Edit Services, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1340, Folder 43)
  - Restructurinh: Fortune, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 1)
  - Restructuring: Internal Consulting Committee, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 2)
  - Restructuring: Life, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 3)
  - Restructuring: Money, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 4)
  - Restructuring: Money [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Restructuring: People, 1986-1987 (Folder 1341, Folder 5)
  - Restructuring: Sports Illustrated, 1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 6)
  - Restructuring: Time, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 7)
  - Retrofit of Time & Life Building Offices, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 8)
  - Reduction in Force, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 9)
  - Reduction in Force [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Rukeyser, Bill, 1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 10)
  - Rybakov, Anatoli: Book, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 11)
  - Rybakov, Anatoli: Book [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R12)
  - Sakharov Book, 1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 12)
  - Salaries: Comparative, 1983 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 13)
  - Salaries: Compensation, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 14)
  - Salaries: Discrimination, 1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 15)
  - Salaries: Researchers, 1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 16)
  - Salaries: Writers, 1988 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 17)
  - Schatz, Arthur, 1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 18)
  - Scott, Foresman, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 19)
  - Security, 1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 20)
  - Sharansky Book, 1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 21)
  - Sharon, Ariel, 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 22)
  - Sharon, Ariel [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Sharon, Ariel: File for Interviews, 1985 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 23)
  - Sharon, Ariel: Press Reaction, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 24-25)
  - Sharon, Ariel: Press Reaction [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Sharon Case: R. Adler, 1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 26)
  - Sharon Case: R. Adler [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Sharon Case: Settlement, 1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 27)
  - Sharon Case: Settlement [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Sheraton, Mimi, 1988 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 28)
  - Simmons Report on Magazine Audiences, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 29-30)
  - Social Events/Guest Lists, 1979-1988 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 31)
  - Southern Progress Corporation, 1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 32)
  - Sports Illustrated: Action Taken, 1985 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 33)
  - Sports Illustrated: Edit Plans, 1987 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 34)
  - Sports Illustrated: New Magazine, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 35)
  - Sports Illustrated: Ray Cave, 1986 (Offsite-box 1341, Folder 36)
  - Sports Illustrated: Miscellaneous, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 1-2)
  - Sports Illustrated for Kids, 1988 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 3)
  - Sports Illustrated for Kids [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Memoranda, 1977-1988 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 4-9)
  - Staff Reduction: General, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 10-11)
  - Staff Reduction: General [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: Discover, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: Edit by Name and Position, 1986 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 12)
  - Staff Reduction: Edit by Name and Position [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: Edit Services, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 13)
  - Staff Reduction: Edit Services [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: Fortune, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 14)
  - Staff Reduction: Fortune [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: Headcount Memoranda, 1986 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 15)
  - Staff Reduction: Life, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 16)
    The unrestricted folder is empty.
  - Staff Reduction: Life [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: Money, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: People [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: Sports Illustrated, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 17)
  - Staff Reduction: Sports Illustrated [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Staff Reduction: Time, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 18)
  - Staff Reduction: Time [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Stock Plan Grants, 1984 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 19)
  - Stock Plan Grants [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Stolley, Dick, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 20)
  - Strike Plans, 1976-1986 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 21)
  - Summer Editorial Interns, 1984-1988 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 22)
  - Summer Editorial Interns [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Sutton, Kelso, 1986 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 23)
  - Syndication of Photographs, 1988 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 24-27)
  - Syndication of Photographs [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Talent, 1987 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 28)
  - Taxi Problems, 1987 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 29)
  - Threats, 1986 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 30)
  - Television Projects, 1985 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 31)
  - Temp Help, 1986-1988 (Offsite-box 1342, Folder 32)
  - Temp Help [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
- Series III.A. Corporate Editor Jason McManus Files, 1980-1987; 2.5 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
  Jason McManus started at Time Inc. in 1957 as a summer trainee, and Time Inc. hired him in 1959. He held various writing and editor positions with Time rising to Executive Editor in 1978. Richard Stolley then McManus temporarily served on a corporate editorial assignment as rotating Assistant Corporate Editor from around June 1981 to November 1982 according to the Department Head Lists in the Time Inc. Reference Files. While serving at the corporate editorial level, McManus retained his regular title as Time Executive Editor. Since McManus held the temporary assignment after Stolley and also later became the permanent Corporate Editor, it appears that many files from the temporary assignment during this time span were taken over by his office. According to a transfer form, his office sent them to the Time Inc. Archives in 1987 which is when McManus was promoted from Corporate Editor to Editor-in-Chief.
  Citation:
  These are a mix of office files created by the rotating corporate editorial position held by Richard Stolley, Jason McManus, and David Maness, and are primarily McManus's along with some of his files while he was Corporate Editor. The files are accompanied by a file list titled "Files from Rm 34-06." Files include reports on possible new magazines, reports on individual magazine activity on radio and television, correspondence among the editorial staff, conference and national organization materials, personnel policies, and various committee agendas and notes.
  Organized alphabetically based on the original order on the file transfer forms.
  - Box #1: File Transfer Form, 1987 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 1)
  - Box #1: Original File List, 1983 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 2)
  - Box #1: Adult Programming (On Cable), 1984 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 3)
  - Box #1: Affirmative Action, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 4-7)
  - Box #1: American Renewal TV, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 8-9)
  - Box #1: ATEX, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 10)
  - Box #1: Cable Magazine, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 11-12)
  - Box #1: Cable Magazine Resumes, 1981 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 13)
  - Box #1: CM&D [Corporate Manufacturing and Distribution] Committee, 1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 14)
  - Box #1: Crutcher Committee, 1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 15)
  - Box #1: Data Base, 1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 16)
  - Box #1: Vic DiGiovanni's Developmental Idea, 1984 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 17)
  - Box #1: Discover, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 18)
  - Box #1: Discover Television, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 19)
  - Box #1: Donner, Michael, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 20)
  - Box #1: Edit Liason Committee, 1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 21)
  - Box #1: Electric Photo Committee, 1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 22)
  - Box #1: Electronic Magazine Presentation, 1982 (Offsite-box 1058, Folder 23)
  - Box #1: Fisher: Electronic Publishing Task Force, 1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 1)
  - Box #1: Fortune, 1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 2)
  - Box #1: Fortune Television, 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 3)
  - Box #1: FYI, 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 4)
  - Box #1: Greenbrier Presentation (4As), 1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 5)
  - Box #1: High Tech Show, undated (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 6)
  - Box #1: Home Box Office [HBO], 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 7)
  - Box #1: Lelievre Memos, 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 8)
  - Box #1: Library (Electronic), 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 9)
  - Box #1: Library (Electronic) [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Box #1: Life, 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 10)
  - Box #1: Life Television [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Box #1: Magazine Committee, 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 11)
  - Box #1: Management Development Strategy and Management Inventory, 1983 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 12)
  - Box #1: Management Development Strategy and Management Inventory: Steed, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 13)
  - Box #1: March of Time, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 14)
  - Box #1: March of Time [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Box #1: Martin, Chuck, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 15-16)
  - Box #1: Mastheads, 1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 17)
  - Box #1: Massachusetts Institute of Technology [MIT], 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 18)
  - Box #1: Retrofitting of Building, 1985 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 19)
  - Box #2: File Transfer Form, 1987 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 20)
  - Box #2: Legal [RESTRICTED], 1981-1982 (Offsite-box R14)
  - Box #2: Magazine Development, 1984 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 21)
  - Box #2: Money: Newsletter (The New Strategist), 1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 22)
  - Box #2: Money: TV, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 23)
  - Box #2: National News Council, 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 24-25)
  - Box #2: National News Council [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R14)
  - Box #2: News Service, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 26)
  - Box #2: Palm Beach Presentation (Association of National Advertisers, Inc.), 1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 27)
  - Box #2: People, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 28)
  - Box #2: People: TV, 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 29)
  - Box #2: Personnel, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 30)
  - Box #2: Sears II, 1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 31)
    Regarding Olympics inserts.
  - Box #2: Sony, 1982 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 32)
  - Box #2: Sports Illustrated: TV, 1981 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 33)
  - Box #2: Sports Illustrated, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 1059, Folder 34)
  - Box #2: Teletext, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 1-3)
  - Box #2: Time: ATEX Efficiencies, 1982 (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 4)
  - Box #2: Time: TV, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 5)
  - Box #2: Trainees: A. Hood, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 6)
  - Box #2: TV and the Magazines, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1200, Folder 7-8)
- Series III.B. Corporate Editor Gilbert Rogin Files, 1960-1992; 1.75 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
  Gilbert "Gil" Rogin started at Time Inc. in 1955 as Sports Illustrated newsmarker at the clipping desk. He worked his way up at Sports Illustrated becoming the Managing Editor in 1982. In 1983, Rogin briefly held a corporate editorial position as a special assistant to Editor-in-Chief Henry Grunwald. This may have been part of the rotating program to give various managing editors experience in the corporate editorial office. In 1984, he became the Discover Managing Editor and stayed in this position until its closure. He took over as Corporate Editor in 1987, replacing Jason McManus.
  This series contains Gilbert Rogin's Subject and Personnel files during his tenure as Corporate Editor.
  Organized into three subseries based on the folder list transferring the materials to the Time Inc. Archives:
  Subseries III.B.1. Accompanying Folder List
  Subseries III.B.2. Subject Files
  Subseries III.B.3. Personnel Files
  - Subseries III.B.1. Accompanying Folder List, undated; 0.1 Linear feet in 1 folder
    This item is an undated folder list that accompanied the materials in the other subseries of Series III.B.
    This series is a single item.
    - Accompanying Folder List, undated (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 1)
  - Subseries III.B.2. Subject Files, 1972-1992; 0.75 Linear feet in 1 record carton
    This series includes correspondence and meroranda to and from staff; article proposals; the original Entertainment Weekly prospectus and business plan; and management meeting summaries. Topics discussed in correspondence include new company programs and policies; the disbursement of Discover staff after closure; and obtaining credentials for Olympics coverage.
    Retains the original alphabetical order from the accompanying folder list.
    - Berne Copyright Convention, 1987 (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 2)
    - Bureaucracy Memorandum, 1985 (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 3)
    - Cafeteria, 1988 (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 4)
    - Condoms, 1987-1988 (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 5)
    - Conflict of Interest, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 6)
    - Discover, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 7)
    - Edit Services: Questionnaires and Managing Editor Responses, 1987 (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 8)
    - Entertainment Magazine and Jeff Jarvis, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1391, Folder 9)